[{"answer": "We never dated in winter", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Reverse-Peephole.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Oh, I walked by my friend's the other day, and I saw that massage chair we want to get my friend as an apartment gift", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Hey", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Reverse-Peephole.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "What, has my friend got another army man stuck in his ear", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "What do you want? I'm in the middle of something", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Reverse-Peephole.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "What? What are you talking about", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "No, I don't have it yet", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Reverse-Peephole.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "No, I brought a picture of the chair", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Ready to go", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Reverse-Peephole.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "You don't go that often", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "All set. I can't believe I'm going dancing", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Reverse-Peephole.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "No, because it's so stupid. Shall we? my friend handing him a bunch of miscellaneous items that would seem to normally go in her purse", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "No. No. It's a small men's carryall", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Reverse-Peephole.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "It's not a purse. It's European. my friend sits down with my friend", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Don't you have ", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Reverse-Peephole.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Cool", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Then who", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Reverse-Peephole.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "my friend", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Yeah, something like that. my friend in his apartment with my friend", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Reverse-Peephole.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "All you have to do is wear the fur so my friend thinks it's yours", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Because of your giant wallet. Just get rid of it", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Reverse-Peephole.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Your good friend is morbidly obese", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Hey, my friend, just out for a little stroll in my favorite fur coat", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Reverse-Peephole.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "It sure is", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "No, that's not your coat", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Reverse-Peephole.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "It's my friend's coat", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "If that is not his coat, whose coat is it", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Reverse-Peephole.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Who's my friend", "qsentId": 28}]